[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Senator, it's almost too much to bear, isn't it, listening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "What do you say to those who say, I have my Second Amendment rights, I'm entitled to bear arms, you are not entitled to take away that right by removing these kind of weapons from the streets and from the stores?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "You -- there is no Second Amendment right to bear every type of weapon that you know of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "That this may be as some are hoping a tipping point for the American public opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Yes, I hope so, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Are you proud of what you said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "It's just a fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Do you think this is a time to talk about guns being fun when 20 children aged 5 years old are being blown to pieces by a weapon that is freely available in this country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "WRB", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, you need to ask the reporter, because he was the one that approached me with the particular questions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Why does anybody in America who is not in the military or the police force need a semiautomatic weapon that can unleash hundreds of shots in a matter of a few minutes and slaughter innocent Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "We do understand it's not a machine gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Why you persist in wanting this to be freely available to Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, automobiles kill more people on our streets than guns do, but we don't say we shouldn't have them because some maniac that's drunk ends up driving a car into a family and killing them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "You're quite happy with where things are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RBS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Well, most of it is either suicides or criminal on criminal shootings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you know that figure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I don't because the FBI clumps it together with suicides.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "You think -- so you believe this theory that if everyone in that movie theater was armed, they would have all stood up and shot him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Not everyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How many do you want to be armed in that movie theater?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I believe somebody firing at him would have slowed him down or possibly stopped him, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "And they're highly trained -- yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "How many suicides do they have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Eleven to 12,000 murders from guns a year in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan", "America"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "And you still don't care, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Suicides are higher in Japan than they are in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "But what should that something be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "IN", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I think it's a multitude of things, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Would you like to see a ban on both of those things, as Senator Feinstein is trying to push through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Yes, I absolutely would.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Feinstein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How do you think the community is doing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "They're very strong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "And as people are watching this and want to know how they can help, what is the best way for people outside of Newtown to contribute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, to contribute I think for our country, because it's really about our country, if it's only Newtown that goes through these changes and tries to effect these things, that's one small part.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "How you doing physically, first of all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I'm slowly recovering.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "What were your feelings when you heard about the scale of what had happened coming so soon after what happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yes, I mean, I saw the initial reports like everyone did that maybe just the shooter had been killed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "You actually live literally 10 minutes away, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Yes, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "What does this say about America that you're attacked in a movie theater by a young man with an AR-15 assault rifle and then 10 minutes away from where you live, an elementary school is shot up with a young man with exactly the same weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "I think it's certainly discouraging in some sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What did he say to you then, Dave, and what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "We were all gathered in Aurora, and we were sitting in the room, waiting for the president to arrive.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "What do you say to the parents in Sandy Hook now who are trying to somehow deal with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "We are behind them 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I say to them it's not about their Second Amendment rights.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "It was an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "It was an AR-15.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "That's not the correct debate, it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "No, actually, it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "He saw two students killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "She was shot dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "She was shot dead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Why are the Americans so reluctant to collectively rise up and demand action, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Because I think it really takes somebody in our position, once we've lost somebody, once we've known somebody who is injured and are -- they've got lasting post traumatic stress syndrome, to really see the effects and damages it causes, because it's unfortunately a very unique club.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "If there is one thing you could say to people about guns, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "God, Piers, put me on the spot here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "How many are children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]